# Hi, I'm Joseph Onipede.



### **Professional Summary**

I am an experienced personnel in the development of web applications & mobile apps. What really got me into the field, though, is the passion I have for it, and my eagerness to learn more has been making me scale through the journey. Throughout my endeavor, I've noticed that I've always been good at what I do. Outside work, I spend an unhealthy amount of time writing code, running, taking long naps, and obsessing over algorithmic optimization. Moving forward, I plan to expand my experience across different industries.

# **Experience**

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER Aug 2022 - Current Placid Global International, Maryland, Lagos

- I converted Figma designs to beautiful, responsive, and interactive Ui.
- Consumption of API with architectures like MCV, MVP, MVVM & Clean Architecture.
- I worked with backend developers on various projects.
- I ensured that integrations worked smoothly.
- I Implemented various functions on different mobile apps.

**MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER** Jun 2022 - Current Brightstar Integral Technology Solutions, Ikeja, Lagos

- Screen conversions.
- Consumption of API.
- Working with product designers and backend developers on various projects.
- Using modern architectures to run implementations.
- Implementation of various functions on different mobile apps.

WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER Apr 2021 - Jan 2023

Dartechlabs, Ozoro, Delta

Ó

- Planned website development, converting mockups into a usable web presence.
- Provided front-end website development with back-end.
- Created API & custom mobile applications using native technologies.
- Devised documentation for each app, detailing operation aspects, functions, capabilities, and features.

BACKEND DEVELOPER Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

EsClass Org, Ojo, Lagos

#### **Contact**

- +2348105902536
- onipedejoseph2018@gm ail.com
- 18, Akogun street, Etegbin , Ojo, Lagos 102101 Nigeri a

#### Skills

- Debug software
- Update software
- Produce clean code
- Develop specifications
- Evaluate user requirements
- Motivation
- Networking
- · Creative thinking
- Problem-solving
- Verbal communication
- Teamwork
- Write programs
- Prioritization

## Languages

English, Fluent

- Discussed project aims with the development team.
- I designed and built web API with Laravel.
- Worked with the front-end developers on projects.
- Performed unit testing and ensured that integrations worked smoothly.
- Recorded and reported work done so far.

# **Education**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - ELECTRONICS AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Oct 2024

Lagos State University, Ojo, Lagos